Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ngthinhducnguyen (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/ngthinhducnguyen (Portfolio)

Top Skills

User Interface Prototyping Figma (Software)
User Interface Design

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)
English (Limited Working)

Certifications

Certificate On The Job Training Certificate On The Job Training Visual Design assessment Figma Assessment

Honors-Awards

Project Award

Thinh Nguyen

UI/UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

My name is Thinh Nguyen, I am a UI/UX Designer.I have had about 1 year working on different projects.I create my products with an interest in user convenience, arranging ideas, layout logically, user-friendly for the best performance and aesthetics.

I always emphasize discipline and professional work to create good products for users, while adding value to the company and enhancing my own value. The challenge in the professional environment is the next step to help me get closer to my goals. Thank you for taking the time, I am eager to connect with you further. I can be reached at: (+84) 96 697 6120 or ngthinhducnguyen@gmail.com

Experience

MindX Technology School 2 years 4 months

Research & Learning: UI/UX Design Company Bootcamp June 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)

 Design interface and user experience for app accumulating gift exchange points

Research & Learning: UX/UI Design Intensive March 2023 - May 2023 (3 months)

 Build a focused teaching management system for teachers and mentors at Mindx Technology School.

Research & Learning: UI/UX Design for Everyone December 2022 - February 2023 (3 months)

• E-commerce application for the sale of furniture.

Công ty cổ phần thương mại và dịch vụ Sao Kim Graphic Designer/3D Visualizer January 2021 - Present (4 years 3 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- 3D design of interior products
- Describe space, render architectural and interior images
- Repair and divide the interior image
- Support building and development of software, applications for the interior industry

Freelance

1 year 8 months

3D Visualizer

May 2021 - December 2022 (1 year 8 months)

- 3D design of interior products
- Describe space, render architectural and interior images
- · Repair and divide the interior image

Graphic Designer

May 2021 - December 2022 (1 year 8 months)

- Design of banner, poster, standee...
- · Design of brand identification.

Công ty TNHH thời trang Red Sun

Graphic Designer/3D Visualizer

December 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Design of banner, poster, standee...
- Photograph of product
- Kiosk layout to display products at events, stands

Education

MindX Technology School

UI/UX Design · (December 2022 - August 2023)

Nova Education

Bachelor's degree, Interior Design · (August 2018 - October 2020)